Hey!
I can't believe I was
killed by a stray bullet...
You can't die here!
What about your dream?!
Sagara Yoshiharu, was it?
My dream to have a country and
a castle, and all the girls...
You fulfill it!
What?
You can do it, Yoshiharu!
Wait!
I still don't even know your name!
My name is Kinoshita Toukichiro.
Toukichiro?
You're Toyotomi Hideyoshi!
Don't die!
If you die, history will get all messed up!
You're supposed to serve
Nobunaga and unite Japan!
Nobunaga?
The lord of the Oda is Oda Nobuna...
No!
What is this?
Oh, right. It's a dream.
I'm a big fan of Lord Oda
Nobunaga's Ambition,
and I fell asleep while I
was playing the game.
A girl?
Crap!
Your life is mine!
Stop right there!
You can't do that to a hot girl!
It's a waste!
Are you an Oda Soldier, too?
Where's your weapon?
Uh oh.
I didn't think that far.
Finish them already!
Right!
Anything!
I need to find something...
Th-The enemy?
A downloadable extra for LONA.
Voices of Battle!
He's got an army in that little box?
Is he a magic user?
Surprised?
Then...
I forgot to charge it!
Go! Kill them both!
Damn it!
Game over already?
But if I can protect her...
No! It's Onishibata!
We almost got the Oda general!
Withdraw!
The Oda general?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Keep pressing forward
and rout the Imagawa.
And you...
Get off me already!
How dare a mere ashigaru soldier
push down the head of the Oda family?
The head of the family is Oda Nobunaga.
Who's Nobunaga?
I'm the head of the Oda family,
Oda Nobuna.
Episode One
It is the age of the civil wars.
The land is divided by powerful warlords,
who fight each other constantly.
Ou'u - Yonezawa Castle
Any internal power struggle is an
invitation for your neighbors to attack.
Kai - Tsutsujigasaki Castle
So it is decided that the firstborn child,
regardless of gender, would
become the head of the family.
Suruga - Sunpu Castle
Owari - Kiyosu Castle
The result of this was the birth
of the Princess Generals.
No way.
You're Katsuie?
Shibata Katsuie
The fierce Shibata Katsuie.
Her nickname is Riku.
Is there some problem?
N-No...
The Katsuie I know from my games
is an old guy with a beard...
Wh-What's wrong with you?
Stop staring at my breasts!
Uh, sorry.
They're just so big, I couldn't help myself.
How rude!
Stop that.
If nothing else, he saved my life.
I still can't believe Oda
Nobunaga is a girl...
I understand that that strange
technique you used isn't magic.
Is it some kind of barbarian technology?
Technique?
Oh, the ringtone?
It's out of batteries,
so I can't use it anymore.
Aw.
I thought you might be kind of interesting.
So?
You want to serve the Oda family?
Please, Nobunaga-sama, let—
What? What was that?
You messed up the name of the
general you want to serve?!
Are you an idiot?!
I told you my name is Nobuna!
So what's your name?
I said tell me!
I hate slow people.
Come on, tell me!
Sagara Yoshiharu!
It's Monkey. Got it.
It's Sagara Yoshiharu!
I'm from the future,
so I'm practically a god—
The future?! Hah!
I don't believe in gods or buddhas.
And somebody who says something
so weird isn't even human.
So I've decided you're a monkey.
So we can call him Monkey then.
But if we're going to use him as a
retainer, he needs some kind of position.
Niwa Nagahide
Niwa Nagahide.
Her nickname is Manchiyo.
The Oda family's tactician.
You're right.
It felt good to step on him.
So he can be in charge of my shoes.
That will do nicely.
Seventy points.
For what reason?!
I'm a monkey and in charge of your shoes?!
Does her calling me "monkey" mean
I'm supposed to take his place?
The same name Nobunaga gave Toyotomi
Hideyoshi, the man who united Japan...
So you failed to slay that idiot Oda?
Imagawa Yoshimoto
Imagawa Yoshimoto.
Ruler of the eastern coastal provinces,
and the daimyo closest to conquering Japan.
I'm terribly sorry.
We almost had her and then
somebody interfered...
Matsudaira Motoyasu
Matsudaira Motoyasu.
Later she will become Tokugawa Ieyasu,
but right now she is a mere
servant of the Imagawas.
I'll have to cut your pay
again as punishment.
Not that!
I'm already eating nothing but
potatoes four days a week...
Is that you, Hanzou?
The one who interfered is called
Monkey by the Oda clan.
So she hired a monkey?
Nobuna is such a fool!
This is kind of shabby.
"Be happy you were even
given a place to stay,"
is what the princess says.
Maeda Toshiie
Maeda Toshiie.
Her nickname is Inuchiyo.
The greatest spear
wielder in the Oda clan.
I was thrown into the civil war
era with nothing of my own,
so I can't ask for too much.
Is it not to your taste?
Old man Asano.
Oh, my, how valiant you look.
You look just like I did as a youth.
So much that I wish you'd marry my
daughter Nene and take over my inn.
Introduce me!
Very well.
I'm Nene!
Nice to meet you, Mr. Monkey!
She's way below my
age range! No, thanks!
You're a very noisy person, Mr. Monkey.
I'm not a monkey.
I'm Sagara Yoshiharu.
I understand, Mr. Monkey.
Whatever...
Intruder!
Damn.
Ow.
What's going on?
My name is Hachisuka Goemon.
I've come to serve you in place
of my master Kinoshita...
Another little girl?
How rude.
I'm not good with long sentences.
Are you Toukichiro's daughter?
His companion!
He is the trunk, and I am the
vine hiding in its shade.
Together we will make
our way in the world.
That was our promise.
So you can do, like, thirty or so letters, tops.
Shut up!
A promise you made with Tokichirou, huh?
With no idea of how to get home,
I'll have to survive here.
It sucks that it's not Nobunaga,
just some snippy little
girl named Nobuna,
but saving a pretty girl and conquering
Japan doesn't sound so bad.
Just wait, old man.
From now on, I'll take your place!
Yoshitatsu plans on attacking Oda.
He's still young.
Saitou Dousan
Saitou Dousan, the daimyo of Mino.
A legend of the civil wars,
who started as a merchant and
grew to rule an entire province.
Nobuhide, the tiger of
Owari Province, has died.
And the one who rose in his place...
...is a foolish girl with a taste
for barbarian fashions.
Normally, she would make
an excellent target.
Indeed. If you leave it
to Yoshitatsu and us,
we shall destroy her immediately.
I would take the opposite
route, and become friends.
Impossible!
To do what others would never consider.
That's what it takes to conquer the land.
The Viper of Mino Province
has requested an audience.
The Viper? You mean Saitou Dousan?
Scripted event time!
But Mino Province is a rival of ours.
It's not surprising.
Wh-Why?
Because if I was going to ally with
somebody, it would be the Viper.
You didn't believe I was
from the future, did you?
And?
I'll prove it.
You'll be meeting with Saitou
Dousan at Shoutokuji Temple.
What are you talking about?
We haven't decided where
we're going to meet yet.
Reporting.
Mino Province just gave us the
location of the conference.
Where is it?
Shoutokuji Temple, I'm told.
Impossible.
What a surprise.
Ninety points.
Monkey, how did you know?
How much time do you think I spent...
...playing the game Lord
Oda Nobunaga's Ambition?
The meeting at Shoutokuji
is a mega-famous event in it.
M-Mega... eve...?
Is that barbarian language?
Monkey language.
You brought a lot of them.
500 riflemen. Pretty impressive, right?
I brought them to show off to the Viper.
Come to think of it,
Dousan sees Nobunaga heading
to the meeting, and...
If we kill Nobuna here,
Owari Province will belong
to the Saitou family.
Akechi Mitsuhide
Akechi Juubei Mitsuhide, famous for
her literary and military talent.
A young genius who has begun
to distinguish herself.
Do you think it will be that easy?
Of course.
Everything is ready.
Hey, Nobuna.
You address your lord like that?
Whatever. Have your men light their rifles.
What if the rifles explode?
Are your men that pathetic?
Of course not!
Don't underestimate us!
Trouble!
Impossible!
Impressive.
She had the rifles lit despite the
fact that they might explode.
She's either a complete fool, or...
She's late.
Dousan-sama, you really shouldn't dress
like that during an important meeting.
She'll do the same.
Making the other person feel at ease
is part of being a great leader.
So he was watching.
Anyway, that girl next to him is cute.
There you are, Viper.
What?
No way!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Why?
But you're so beautiful...
Did I surprise you?
Well?
What the hell?!
She's stunning!
Why did you change your clothes?
I'm meeting the Viper of Mino.
I can't wear my usual outfit.
I see.
These two...
Dousan tried to make Nobuna feel at ease,
and Nobuna showed respect for Dousan.
You seem to have brought
a lot of riflemen.
It's the age of rifles now.
Many call them barbarian toys.
My ashigaru soldiers will defeat anybody
stupid enough to say that in a single shot.
The Owari Province soldiers are
said to be the weakest in Japan,
but with rifles in their hands,
they're the strongest.
Someday those rifles will destroy
the strongest cavalry of the
civil wars, the Takeda cavalry.
Man, I'm so excited, I'm shaking!
After you've allied with me,
will you attack Suruga Province and Imagawa?
No. Mino.
Why focus on Mino Province?
The same reason you did, Viper.
The one who rules Mino
Province rules the nation.
Kyou       Mino       Musashi
It's the center of Japan,
dividing the east and west.
Build a well-constructed castle here
and the nation is as good as yours.
To make a wealthy country there,
where merchants may move freely.
That was your ambition, wasn't it?
So you know everything, then?
I'm taking Mino Province.
Do you think I'll give it to you?
What if I told you I'll carry on your dream?
What?
I'll destroy all the old systems
that have wreaked havoc in Japan,
and turn this into a country that can
compete with the barbarian nations.
My focus is turned towards the whole world.
You're a little brat,
but I could see letting you
conquer the whole of Japan!
So your gaze already lies beyond the sea?
Your ideals are correct.
But no one can follow you there.
The fact that they call you
a fool is proof of that.
Even so, I'll keep going forward.
Destroying anything that gets in your way?
If you wish to start with Mino,
then I accept your challenge.
That's what I want.
Wait just a second!
You fool!
Do you want to get killed?!
Get back, Monkey!
Saitou Dousan!
I know what you're thinking!
Stop being so stubborn when you
know what lies in store for Mino!
What are you talking about?
This will be entertaining.
Let him speak.
Monkey...
It's fine.
Let me do this.
One wrong word and your head
will be lying on the floor.
Apologize, Monkey!
There's still time...
Dousan, when this meeting is over,
you'll tell your men this:
"My children shall tie their horses
at the gate of the fool of Owari."
Wh-What?
In other words, you already know
your son can't defeat Nobuna.
You know it can't happen!
Child, how did you read my mind?
I just knew, is all.
What?!
I'm from the future.
You're going to hand Mino over to Nobuna.
If you don't, your entire
life will have been a waste.
Saitou Dousan, Oda Nobuna is the only
one who can continue your dream!
Child...
I have completely lost.
Viper...
I didn't expect anyone from the future.
450 years in the future.
There, Saitou Dousan is a
hero of the civil wars.
Is he?
I wrote my name in the
annals of history, then.
Thanks to you, the Viper has become
true to himself at the very end.
I will prepare a treaty handing
Mino Province over to Nobuna-chan.
I will give Mino to my new
daughter, Nobuna!
Really?
Thus, Owari and Mino Provinces
formed an alliance...
Have you gone mad, Father?!
I refuse to accept it!
I guess I'll praise you for this.
It's thanks to you.
Look at my face and say it.
Shut up, already!
Just give me my shoes.
We're leaving.
Oh, these?
Why were you keeping them there?!
It's a misunderstanding!
I wouldn't want them to be
cold when you put them on!
You were getting off on the
smell of my feet, weren't you?
I've never seen such a pervert!
The mere fact that you're alive is a sin.
I'll kill you here!
Perverted monkey!
Prepare to die, Monkey!